Finding Aid of America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee Record Group SR.198
State Archives of North Carolina
- Assistant Director's Office County File, 1982-1987; SR.198.8; 198.9; 4047; Correspondence; 2.00; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources
  - Sampson, 1984-1985, undated; SR.198.8.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Sampson)
  - Scotland, 1982-1985, undated; SR.198.8.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Scotland)
  - Stanly, 1982-1984, 1986, undated; SR.198.8.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Stanly)
  - Stokes, 1982-1984, 1986, undated; SR.198.8.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Stokes)
  - Surry, 1982-1984, undated; SR.198.8.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Surry)
  - Swain, 1982-1984, undated; SR.198.8.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Swain)
  - Transylvania, 1982, 1984, undated; SR.198.8.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Transylvania)
  - Tyrrell, 1983-1986; SR.198.8.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Tyrrell)
  - Union, 1982-1985, undated; SR.198.8.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Union)
  - Vance, 1982-1984; SR.198.8.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Vance)
  - Wake: General Correspondence, 1973, 1976, 1981-1986, undated; SR.198.8.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Wake: General Correspondence)
  - Wake: Raleigh Committee for the Celebration of the Roanoke Voyage, 1984, undated; SR.198.8.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Wake: Raleigh Committee for the Celebration of the Roanoke Voyage)
  - Warren, 1982-1985; SR.198.8.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Warren)
  - Washington, 1982-1984, 1986, undated; SR.198.8.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Washington)
  - Watauga, 1982-1985, undated; SR.198.8.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Watauga)
  - Wayne: General Correspondence, 1982-1987, undated; SR.198.8.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Wayne: General Correspondence)
  - Wayne: Goldsboro City Schools Lesson Plan, 1986; SR.198.8.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Wayne: Goldsboro City Schools Lesson Plan)
  - Wilkes, 1983-1985, undated; SR.198.8.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Wilkes)
  - Wilson, 1982-1985, undated; SR.198.8.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Wilson)
  - Yadkin, 1982-1987, undated; SR.198.8.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Yadkin)
  - Yancey, 1982, 1984; SR.198.8.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Yancey)
- Correspondence File, 1976 - 1989; SR.198.9; 198.8; 4046; Correspondence; 2.00; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources
  Correspondence and memorandums from various state agencies, committee members, as well as correspondence with various offices and agencies in Great Britain (about royal visits and museum exhibitions). Also includes correspondence concerning book and pamphlet contract agreements.
  RS No. 4046
  - Books, 114; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee
    - Armitage, Christopher: Sir Walter Raleigh Bibliography, 1983-1987, undated; SR.198.9.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Armitage, Christopher: Sir Walter Raleigh Bibliography)
    - Hulton, Paul: The John White Drawings, 1981-1983; SR.198.9.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Hulton, Paul: The John White Drawings)
    - Phelps, David: The Carolina Algonkians, 1983; SR.198.9.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Phelps, David: The Carolina Algonkians)
    - Quinn, David Beers: The First English Colonies in America, 1982-1983; SR.198.9.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Quinn, David Beers: The First English Colonies in America)
    - Quinn, David Beers: Set Fair for Roanoke: Voyages and Colonies, 1584-1606, 1982-1985, undated; SR.198.9.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Quinn, David Beers: Set Fair for Roanoke: Voyages and Colonies, 1584-1606)
    - Stick, David: Roanoke Island: The Beginning of English America, 1981-1984, undated; SR.198.9.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Stick, David: Roanoke Island: The Beginning of English America)
  - Correspondence, 115; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee
    - Basnight, Marc, 1980, 1982-1983, 1985; SR.198.9.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Basnight, Marc)
    - Bicton Park (Sandra George, Public Relations Officier), 1982-1984; SR.198.9.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Bicton Park (Sandra George, Public Relations Officier))
    - Bone, John S., 1981, 1983; SR.198.9.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Bone, John S.)
    - Brave New World Conference, 1978-1979; SR.198.9.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Brave New World Conference)
    - British Liaison, 1978, 1981-1985, 1987, undated; SR.198.9.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder British Liaison)
    - Creber, Goodrich (Devon County Council, England), 1981, 1983; SR.198.9.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Creber, Goodrich (Devon County Council, England))
    - Dorsey, Patricia, 1985; SR.198.9.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Dorsey, Patricia)
    - East Devon District Council, 1981-1983; SR.198.9.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder East Devon District Council)
    - Exeter Cathedral (Very Rt. Rev. Richard Eyre), 1983-1984; SR.198.9.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Exeter Cathedral (Very Rt. Rev. Richard Eyre))
    - Gallop, S. Clyde, 1984; SR.198.9.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Gallop, S. Clyde)
    - Gilbert, Mrs. Walter Raleigh, 1976, 1981-1986; SR.198.9.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Gilbert, Mrs. Walter Raleigh)
    - Goddard, Rev. Canon Paul, 1981-1983; SR.198.9.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Goddard, Rev. Canon Paul)
    - Green, Paul, 1981; SR.198.9.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Green, Paul)
    - Griffith, Andy, 1981-1985, undated; SR.198.9.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Griffith, Andy)
    - Grimsley, Joseph W., 1980-1982; SR.198.9.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Grimsley, Joseph W.)
    - Harmon, Carolyn, 1982-1983; SR.198.9.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Harmon, Carolyn)
    - Hodgkins, Sarah W., 1980-1984, undated; SR.198.9.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Hodgkins, Sarah W.)
    - Hunt, James B., Jr., 1981-1984, undated; SR.198.9.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Hunt, James B., Jr.)
    - Jones, H. G., 1978, 1980-1982, 1984-1987; SR.198.9.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Jones, H. G.)
    - Kennedy, John P., Jr., 1982-1984, 1986-1987; SR.198.9.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Kennedy, John P., Jr.)
    - Kirkham, Reverend (Lord Bishop of Sherborne), 1980-1983, undated; SR.198.9.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Kirkham, Reverend (Lord Bishop of Sherborne))
    - Martin, James G. (Governor), 1985-1986, undated; SR.198.9.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Martin, James G. (Governor))
    - Mathews, Roger (Mayor of Plymouth, England), 1981, 1983-1986; SR.198.9.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Mathews, Roger (Mayor of Plymouth, England))
    - Mayflower Tapestry Library (Tom Mohr), 1980-1983, undated; SR.198.9.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Mayflower Tapestry Library (Tom Mohr))
    - Morrison, Emma Neal, 1980-1983; SR.198.9.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Morrison, Emma Neal)
    - Oriel College (Sir Zelman Cowen, Provost), SR.198.9.003; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Oriel College (Sir Zelman Cowen, Provost))
    - Owens, Robert V., 1982-1984, 1986; SR.198.9.003; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Owens, Robert V.)
    - Paschal, Herbert R., 1980-1983, 1985, undated; SR.198.9.003; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Paschal, Herbert R.)
    - Powell, William S., 1981-1987, undated; SR.198.9.003; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Powell, William S.)
    - Preyer, Richardson, 1981-1984, undated; SR.198.9.003; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Preyer, Richardson)
    - Publications Subcommittee, 1979-1987, 1989, undated; SR.198.9.003; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Publications Subcommittee)
    - Sherborne Castle (Simon Wingfield Digby), 1982-1985; SR.198.9.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Sherborne Castle (Simon Wingfield Digby))
    - Smy, Andrew F. (Director of Devon Tourism), 1981-1983; SR.198.9.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Smy, Andrew F. (Director of Devon Tourism))
    - Stick, David, 1979-1985, undated; SR.198.9.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Stick, David)
    - Wade, Charles B., Jr., 1980-1985, 1987, undated; SR.198.9.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Wade, Charles B., Jr.)
    - Wallis, Dr. Helen (Dir. Of British Library Map Collection), 1981-1984, 1987, undated; SR.198.9.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Wallis, Dr. Helen (Dir. Of British Library Map Collection))
    - Warren, Lindsay C., Jr., 1981-1984; SR.198.9.004; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Warren, Lindsay C., Jr.)
    - Warren, Lindsay C., Jr., 1985-1987, undated; SR.198.9.005; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Warren, Lindsay C., Jr.)
    - Wilson IV, John B., 1980-1984, 1986, undated; SR.198.9.005; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Wilson IV, John B.)
    - Winberry, Charles, 1980-1984; SR.198.9.005; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Winberry, Charles)
    - Winslow, J. Emmet, 1980-1981, undated; SR.198.9.005; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Winslow, J. Emmet)
    - Young, Dr. Joyce (University of Exter History Dept.), 1981-1984; SR.198.9.005; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Young, Dr. Joyce (University of Exter History Dept.))
  - Memorandums, 116; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee
    - Commission Members, 1981-1987; SR.198.9.005; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Commission Members)
    - Dorsey, Patricia (Secretary of Cultural Resources), 1984-1987, undated; SR.198.9.005; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Dorsey, Patricia (Secretary of Cultural Resources))
    - Hodgkins, Sarah W., 1981-1984; SR.198.9.006; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Hodgkins, Sarah W.)
    - Warren, Lindsay C., Jr., 1983-1984; SR.198.9.006; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Warren, Lindsay C., Jr.)
    - Winslow, Lucille, 1981-1983; SR.198.9.006; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Winslow, Lucille)
  - Pamphlets, 117; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee
    - Arner, Robert D.: "The Roanoke Voyages in Literature", 1978, 1982-1985; SR.198.9.006; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Arner, Robert D.: "The Roanoke Voyages in Literature")
    - Cumming, William B.: "Cartography of Coastal Carolina", 1982, 1987; SR.198.9.006; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Cumming, William B.: "Cartography of Coastal Carolina")
    - General Correspondence, 1981-1983, undated; SR.198.9.006; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder General Correspondence)
    - Harrington, J. C.: "Archaeology and the Enigma of Fort Raleigh", 1982-1984; SR.198.9.006; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Harrington, J. C.: "Archaeology and the Enigma of Fort Raleigh")
    - Hoffman, Paul E.: "Spain and the Raleigh Colonies", 1983-1984, 1986; SR.198.9.006; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Hoffman, Paul E.: "Spain and the Raleigh Colonies")
    - Humber, John L.: "Preparations for the Voyage", 1982, 1984, 1986-1987; SR.198.9.006; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Humber, John L.: "Preparations for the Voyage")
    - Miller, Helen Hill: "Passage to America: How Colonists Reached Roanoke", 1982-1983, 1986; SR.198.9.006; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Miller, Helen Hill: "Passage to America: How Colonists Reached Roanoke")
    - Powell, William S.: "Poetry About Virginia Dare and Related Subjects", 1982, undated; SR.198.9.006; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Powell, William S.: "Poetry About Virginia Dare and Related Subjects")
    - Quinn, David Beers: "The Lost Colonists, Their Fortune and Probable Fate?", 1982, 1984; SR.198.9.006; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Quinn, David Beers: "The Lost Colonists, Their Fortune and Probable Fate?")
    - Shirley, John W.: "Sir Walter Raleigh and the New World", 1982-1983, 1985-1987; SR.198.9.006; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Shirley, John W.: "Sir Walter Raleigh and the New World")
    - Youings, Joyce: "Raleigh Country", 1983, 1986-1987; SR.198.9.006; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Youings, Joyce: "Raleigh Country")
- Minutes File, 1978-1986; SR.198.10; 198.10; 4048; Minutes; 1.00; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources; American Quadricentennial Corporation (Reel America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (AFHAC) and Quadricentennial Minutes File)
  Minutes and attachments concerning the committee (and the earlier version of the committee) and the nonprofit corporation. Includes also financial information and monthly status reports. The bound original minutes of the America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (AFHAC) from August 1978 thru September 1980 and American Quadricentennial Corporation (AQC) from November 1978 thru July 1981 were received from former chairman and president, H. G. Jones to William S. Powell on 6 February 1981. Both the AFHAC and AQC held jointly meetings throughout North Carolina; therefore it is necessary to file both together in chronological order. The anniversary celebration ended officially with Virginia Dare Birthday celebration in Manteo on 18 August 1987 and AQC dissolved in December 1987.
  RS No. 4048
  - AFHAC Minutes, SR.198.10; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee
    - Manteo, 5 August 1978; SR.198.10.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Manteo)
    - Raleigh, 14 November 1978; SR.198.10.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Raleigh)
    - Manteo, 17-18 August 1979; SR.198.10.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Manteo)
    - Raleigh, 6 November 1979; SR.198.10.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Raleigh)
    - Chapel Hill, 29 February-1 March 1980; SR.198.10.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Chapel Hill)
    - Manteo, 27-28 June 1980; SR.198.10.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Manteo)
    - Manteo, 19-20 September 1980; SR.198.10.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Manteo)
    - Greenville, 16-17 January 1981; SR.198.10.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Greenville)
    - Raleigh, 26-27 March 1981; SR.198.10.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Raleigh)
    - Manteo, 10-11 July 1981; SR.198.10.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Manteo)
    - Raleigh, 9-10 October 1981; SR.198.10.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Raleigh)
    - Raleigh, 22-23 January 1982; SR.198.10.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Raleigh)
    - Kill Devil Hills, 11-12 June 1982; SR.198.10.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Kill Devil Hills)
    - Raleigh, 5 August 1982; SR.198.10.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Raleigh)
    - Winston-Salem, 3 December 1982; SR.198.10.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Winston-Salem)
    - Charlotte, 18-19 March 1983; SR.198.10.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Charlotte)
    - Nags Head, 17-18 June 1983; SR.198.10.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Nags Head)
    - Goldsboro, 8-9 September 1983; SR.198.10.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Goldsboro)
    - Raleigh, 2-3 December 1983; SR.198.10.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Raleigh)
    - Raleigh, 24 August 1984; SR.198.10.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Raleigh)
    - Manteo, 29 September 1984; SR.198.10.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Manteo)
    - Manteo, 22 February 1985; SR.198.10.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Manteo)
    - Raleigh, 13 September 1985; SR.198.10.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Raleigh)
    - Raleigh, 14 February 1986; SR.198.10.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Raleigh)
    - Raleigh, 28 August 1986; SR.198.10.002; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Raleigh)
  - AQC Minutes, SR.198.10; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee
    - Chapel Hill, 1 November 1978; SR.198.10.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Chapel Hill)
    - Raleigh, 14 November 1978; SR.198.10.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Raleigh)
    - Manteo, 17 August 1979; SR.198.10.001; Department of Natural and Cultural Resources. America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee (Folder Manteo)